Xiang Kun, what are you doing?
Xiang Kun!
You still dare to rebel?
Young Master.
Li Xiao just shot his own man.
Then another tripped over
the wild boar snare.
Miss Mei walked around in her white dress,
and they were scared out of their wits.
I saw it.
Those guys...
were scared to death by their own fear.
Let's go.
Let's figure out how to play
with them longer.
Chun'er, what happened?
There was a slight incident just now.
But luckily, it was just a scare.
I heard gunshots from behind us earlier.
Could Zhang Tianyou and his men
be in trouble?
Young Master!
This won't work!
They've got guns and cannons,
while we've only got shovels
and crappy torches.
We can't fight them head-on.
We need a plan.
Fighting head-on
is for brainless brutes.
Have you forgotten how we started out?
Let's show them our old trade.
Show them what "My turf, my rules" means.
Let's go.
Father, they're over there.
What if there's an ambush?
Father.
In the face of absolute power,
those are just petty tricks.
Alright, we'll do as you say.
Let's go.
Something's wrong.
The magnetic field here is distorted.
Impossible.
Marshal Li.
Look at the soldiers behind you.
Don't they look completely dazed?
This place is filled with natural miasma.
Trying to act tough with me?
I...
Focus! Recite the Heart-Clearing Mantra.
Steady!
Father!
Go!
I'll kill you all!
Father!
Father, are you alright?
I...
I'm not gonna make it.
Li Xiao...
Li Xiao.
You...
must remember...
Father!
Remember what, Father?
Well...
Remember what?
Anyone still breathing?
Follow me.
Zhang Tianyou.
My men have followed your orders
and scattered around.
Guarding the Qian, Kun,
Xun, and Zhen positions.
You exhausted yourself
using the Dragon-Seeking Formula
just to find a piece
of wasteland without even
a single grave mound?
What's the rush, Mei?
Haste makes waste.
Tide, tide...
The key is in the word "Tide."
It's not only hidden in the earth,
but also concealed in time.
We have to wait for this forest to
breathe.
Breathe?
The Dragon-Seeking Formula states,
Dragon's Lair appears at the fated hour.
Yin-Yang Harmony opens the Hidden Court.
Let's wait for this tidal mist to clear.
We'll wait.
Tianyou
Young Master.
Look, this fog is a bit too sinister.
I'm a little scared.
Don't panic.
Stargazing has its methods,
dragon-seeking has its formula.
Seven Stars set the Celestial Pivot,
the Big Dipper points the dragon's path.
Greedy Wolf opens the Dragon Vein,
Martial Star lights the tomb.
Open!
It's really here.
Great.
Shuang'er, Miss Sheng, Chun'er.
All of you women stay outside.
This twenty-year grudge
is for my old bones
and the former chief to go in and settle.
No, Father.
I'm going too.
The dangers inside are unknown.
One more person means more help.
No.
Father!
That's an order.
Fenglin, get your sister ready.
Shuang'er, listen to me.
Use your Yin-Yang Eyes to open the door,
then stay outside with them as backup.
Okay.
Here.
Don't worry.
I'll come back alive
so you can divorce me.
Chun'er.
Wan Chun'er's occipital lobe is
more developed than average.
If she concentrates,
she can see things ordinary people can't.
But it's also extremely draining.
Can you handle it?
This one...
Chun'er.
We only have one chance
to crack this mechanism.
Are you sure?
I'm positive, Tianyou.
It's this one.
We've used one of the
Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye.
Let's go.
Let's see what
the nightmare and truth that have plagued
the four families for 20 years really are.
The mantis stalks the cicada,
but the oriole lurks behind.
Zhang Tianyou.
You really did see all of this coming.
You're still planning to make a move
on Zhang Tianyou?
That's right.
It's either I kill him,
or he kills us.
If he enters that tomb,
he'll find out everything.
Young Master.
So this is the lair of that evil thing.
It's even shabbier than
my cellar back home.
What is all this?
It's been dead for too long,
so long that even the air forgot to flow.
But some things are still
very much alive and kicking.
Patriarch Mei,
we've been walking for a while.
You're holding onto that weapon
of yours pretty tightly.
Watch out, Young Master!
Zhang Tianyou.
You're too smart.
So smart that it's frightening.
You already know too much.
Don't go any further.